ANASTASIIA KIIAS



EDUCATION

06.2023 - 09.2023

UX/UI Designer

Spiced Academy Bootcamp, Berlin

2010 - 2015

MA in Hotel & Restaurant

Business

Zaporizhzhia National University, Ukraine

EXPERTISE

- UI Design
- Prototyping & Wireframing
- Responsive Web Design
- Information Architecture
- User Centered Design
- User Research

SOFTWARE

- Fiama
- Notion
- Framer
- Miro

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian English

Native Professional proficiency Proficiency

UX/UI DESIGNER

anastasiiakiias@gmail.com

+49 176 6956 3538

My LinkedIn

My Portfolio

PROFILE

I am **Berlin-based** UX/UI designer, with a background in hospitality, which has refined my abilities to anticipate user needs and communicate effectively. I am focused on creating exclusive user experience through research and a deep understanding of user needs.

EXPERIENCE

TRANSITION TO GERMANY

2021-2023

Rerlin

- Studied German to B1 level (certificate issued in October, 2023)
- Completed Project Management Industry Training at Brainnest of 20 hours + individual work
- Received Professional Scrum Master™ I (PSM I) at Scrum.org
- Completed 7 courses with Creative Practice (WebDesign, UX/UI, Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator)

BUSINESS CLASS CABIN CREW 2015

2015-2021

Emirates Airline, Dubai

- Proficiently communicated vital instructions to passengers and new team members on every flight with overall of 355 flights during my career, employing verbal and non-verbal techniques.
- Demonstrated quick thinking and problem-solving abilities in challenges during flights with overall of 4778 flying hours, minimizing disruptions and maintaining passenger comfort.